hotstocked.com 2007-12-15

# Privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience with the Hotstocked.com as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to visit our website with complete confidence. 

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how the Hotstocked.com collects information from all end users of our services (the "Services") -- those who access our website and/or receive our newsletter. 

Personal Information Hotstocked.com Collects and How It Is Used 

Introduction 

Hotstocked.com collects information in different ways from Visitors and Subscribers who access the various parts of our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services, and generally share this information with third party investment newsletters for investor relations purposes. Users are always given the opportunity of opting-out of these promotions. We may also disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that law requires such disclosure or other special cases described below. 

Registration 

Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number and email address. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account. This information will be shared with third party marketing partners. Users are always given the opportunity of opting-out of these promotions. 

Hotstocked.com may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, once the partner receives the information, it will handle the information under its own privacy policies. 

Hotstocked.com may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services. 

Online Advertisements 

We share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For instance, an advertiser might tell us the audience they want to reach (for example, males between 25 and 55 years of age) and provide us with an advertisement tailored to that audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to the intended audience. However, Hotstocked.com generally does not share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers unless special circumstances require us to do so. 

Responses to Email Inquiries 

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to Hotstocked.com, we use the return email address to answer the email inquiry we receive. Hotstocked.com does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

Email Marketing From Third Party Sponsors 

When you subscribe to Hotstocked service, your e-mail address will also be added to the following newsletters SmallCapNetwork.com, OTCJournal.com, MicroCapPulse.com, Microstockprofit.com, and Outcasttrader.com. Users are always given the opportunity of opting-out of these promotions, and may unsubscribe to any of these newsletters at any time.   
Other than the aforementioned we do not sell share or otherwise transfer your e-mail to any third party subscribers.

Voluntary Customer Surveys 

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if a third party conducts the survey. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary. 

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses from other Hotstocked.com subscribers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated; non-personally-identifying information may be shared with third parties. 

Special Cases 

It is Hotstocked.com's policy not to use or share personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Hotstocked.com may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect Hotstocked.com and our Members. 

"Cookies" and How Hotstocked.com Uses Them 

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Hotstocked.com may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

Hotstocked.com Commitment to Data Security 

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

Where to Direct Questions About Hotstocked.com Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: 

Hotstocked.com Editor through our [contact form](http://www.hotstocked.com/contact.html "contact form")

Revisions to This Policy 

Hotstocked.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted within the respective section of our site. 

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.
